Globe dropped
Everyone thinks sage is trash today
My goal is to prove that she's the meta
Can i top drag three games in a row
Or will i get reported
Let's find out the freak and cross this bridge bridge bridge bridge bridge bridge
Take this gotta go spike planted last player standing
Dead yes
Oh crazy
My boy
They bought me off bro
They walk me off
I love this guy was doing some grim bro
I thought he was there
Bro
I was like this has got to be some grim
Crap on my head
Player standing a rap flow that i'm out
To rush the dust back to the actions of the dust to flush
We can
With the deck
No idea where the speaker is
You will not kill my allies in
One enemy by ultimate thirty seconds left
Last player standing before you
With the good in the world like down
Yeah
Can be none other time
The mother and nile all conversation standing in our way above complete
And every day is for my love muscle
Cause my verbal trated
You can keep like down
And you got a last layer standing
To point the finger at man
No chance to stand
Need to compete
The snack
The bones like boys ain't no holding back
It's my friends
He used one
D just ran out of
Oh
The bomb
Just shoot it up
You want
You want to jump on
Nah we should have won
That runs out of nah bro
This guy literally ran it
Oh my god
If i
Oh
We were just dying
So i sped it up
Bro that i need
And because i was born on the
As i know
My man
Never to be taken like me
I gotta
Style like when the tai got on the phone
Show up figures that i'm ready for whatever
Whenever fight plan
I do hands up in the air
I'm gonna do my one spot
I thought they were
They may still be all time
You should run and divorce the line before
It's too late
It keeps turning
Don't need to find me
Don't over my bedroom
And nobody else
So i i with electronics
Oh
One of them
Let's let's put on top
Come here
Let's go
I killed two on accident
And i shot the one
And then another one just died
No reward for my swords
Just pay me and smacking them
I think finding a legit
No utai
I don't think we go here
I don't nothing
Nothing nothing
Walk back here
Let me see you psychotic
In the slowest flank of all time
I felt i didn't
I got it
It flanked
Wait he no
He went back
Where are you
Not an alt
Nothing true
Oh
He's funny funny
Now
He's entry reentry
Have you seen rose
The clash
Wait what
Oh my tippy bro
What are we going
I got him
Oh wait
I thought that was from sight
That serious
I think racist
I think racist eyes in the
Oh
I quote on that needs to lock to flip in really
Up
Okay
I'm in the studio on
I'm saying i'm a  on my bed
It's close
But if you run up on my
My boy is a late night
Late night
I walk in the door
Is there
I don't think there's anything about the
Girl
I just keep listening
I can you
You mean a lot
Oh my god
Down one more
You can stop it
We never move
Yeah
You can get that
Must i do
Let's go bro
Let's go as well
Get out of my way
Oh my god
Oh
Wait that little combo
Well one two
One enemy
Oh my god
Oh no wait
Wait
Wait wait no
I'm not gonna do that
I can get on that wal
To what's down
Those you must know about myself
I just my pistol
Yeah
I must promote you
Step up to this look
To the show
To help
Oh
That is a lot of bullets
Because i can't get ahead
Don't smoke
Man
I got that watch our cat
Just watch my cat hit the head
We're falling behind
As if it never fails
It never feels better
Why i'm playing anti
After that
Just to say that the stress is
I can't get ahead
But falling to the get
Oh my god
Five bullets in that kill
Round round
All right
Enough of you
Nice
I suppose like i never left
He's close
You know
Oh no
He does not know
I don't know what i'm doing
I didn't
And i'm
There's something that
One enemy
One last heaven
Let's go bro
Out of my way
Oh my god
Three three three three nice
Yes
Steam go
I don't
I don't give me this
Give me this
Yeah
Flanker
Flanker matt
I'm tripping
I thought i saw my
Oh
Wait
Is it our response
Yeah
Hey guys
If you enjoyed that video
Watch this next one
And also don't forget to follow my twitch stream and watch me live
I'm live every single day
And the link is in the description
All right
I'll see you guys there bye
You guys